Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Anthony P. Monaco administrative records and related papers, 2020 May -- 2020 November; UA001.005335; 2.49 Gigabytes; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Audiovisual materials, 2020 May -- 2020 November; UA001.005336; 2.49 Gigabytes; 7 Digital Object(s)
    This sub-series contains audio-visual material, including university-wide town hall videos and a video recording of a toast to the graduating class of 2020. Town hall videos address policies and updates related to the COVID-19 pandemic, the Equity and Inclusion Workstream, and general campus updates.
    - University-wide town hall meeting audio, 2020 September 24; UA001.005337; 21.05 Megabytes
      Open for research to the Tufts University community.
    - University-wide town hall meeting video, 2020 September 24; UA001.005338; 700.38 Megabytes
    - University-wide town hall meeting audio, 2020 October 19; UA001.005339; 20.15 Megabytes
    - University-wide town hall meeting video, 2020 October 19; UA001.005340; 786.34 Megabytes
    - University-wide town hall meeting chat transcript, 2020 October 19; UA001.005341; 1.55 Kilobytes
    - University-wide town hall meeting video, 2020 November 20; UA001.005342; 595.32 Megabytes
    - Senior Brunch toast video, 2020 May; UA001.005343; 428 Megabytes
  - Michael Baenen records, 2000 September -- 2021 June; UA001.005344; 116 Digital Object(s) 116 mbox files; 38.1 Gigabytes (Laptop MCDCAL13182)
    University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
    Email will be made available to members of the originating office on a DCA laptop in the reading room only.
    This series contains Michael Baenen's email records from his time as Chief of Staff in the President's Office.
- Additional accessions, 1967 -- 2007; UA001.019
  This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  - Hallowell - Inaugural Material, 1967; UA001-015 (Box 1)
    Certificates of greetings upon the appointment to the presidency, to Hallowell from other colleges and universities.
  - Annual Reports and Year in Review, 1993 -- 2000; UA001-017 (Box 2)
  - Mayer - Hoods, UA001-035 (Box 3)
  - Mayer - Hoods, UA001-036 (Box 4)
  - Mayer - robes, degrees, memorabilia, UA001-037 (Box 5)
  - Mayer - diplomas, degrees, 1967 -- 1992; UA001-038 (Box 6)
  - DiBiaggio - Correspondence, Invitation, and Holiday Cards, 1993 -- 1995; UA001-041 (Box 7)
  - Hallowell - Commemorative Footballs, 1969 -- 1976; UA001-042 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Records pertaining to the termination of Navy Systems Coordination Project, 1950 -- 1954; UA001-043 (Box 9)
  - DiBiaggio Photographs and Audio Tape, UA001-046 (Box 10)
  - DiBiaggio Photographs and VHS tape, UA001-048 (Box 11)
  - Gifford House Function Binders, 1997 -- 2007; UA001-049 (Box 12)
  - Gifford House Function Binder and Commencement Binders, 1999 -- 2006; UA001-050 (Box 13)
  - Subject Files, UA001-051 (Box 14)
  - Subject Files, UA001-052 (Box 15)
  - Event Files, 1999 -- 2000; UA001-053 (Box 16)
  - Subject Files and Reports, UA001-054 (Box 17)
  - Financial Files, 1998 -- 1999; UA001-058 (Box 18)
  - Subject and financial files, 1996 -- 1999; UA001-059 (Box 19)
  - Subject Files, 1983 -- 1991; UA001-060 (Box 20)
    Re: Honorary Degrees, Commencement, Speeches, Annual (to the O of the P), Talloires Newsletters and Reports.
  - Subject Files, 1989 -- 1999; UA001-061 (Box 21)
    RE: marketing, university council, trip to Germany.
  - Subject and correspondence files, UA001-062 (Box 22)
    Honorary Degrees and subject and correspondence files.
  - Budget and Subject Files, UA001-063 (Box 23)
  - Budget and Subject Files (including DiBaggio Inauguration), UA001-064 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files, 1997 -- 1998; UA001-065 (Box 25)
  - Shared Visions Newsletter, 1993 -- 1994; UA001-066 (Box 26)
  - Speeches B-Z, 1994 -- 1998; UA001-067 (Box 27)
  - DiBiaggio Speeches and Photographs/Slides, UA001-068 (Box 28)
  - Commencement Binders, Photographs and CD's (Judy Olsen's), 2004 -- 2005; UA001-070 (Box 29)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 2007; UA001-071
  - Robing Ceremony CD 2, 2007; UA001-072
  - Honorary Degree Dinner CD 1 of 3, 2007; UA001-073
  - Honorary Degree Dinner CD 2 of 3, 2007; UA001-074
  - Honorary Degree Dinner CD 3 of 3, 2007; UA001-075
  - 2007 Commencement Pics, UA001-076
  - Robing Ceremony CD 1, 2007; UA001-077
  - President DiBiaggio's Speeches, 2000; UA001-078
  - Judy Olson's Computer Files, 2000-07 -- 2002-07; UA001-079
  - Judy Olson files, 2003 -- 2004; UA001-080
  - Judy Olson files, 2004 -- 2005; UA001-081
  - Judy Olson's email, 2000 -- 2003; UA001-083
  - Leonard Carmichael inaguaration, UA001-093 (Box 30)
  - President's office, UA001-094 (Box 31)
    Statements by Burton Hallowell and John DiBiaggio.
  - President's office, UA001-095 (Box 32)
    Commencement photographs and miscellaneous books.
  - President's office, UA001-096 (Box 33)
    VHS tapes.
  - President's office, UA001-097 (Box 34)
    Awards ceremony and WGBH files.
  - Department of Defense administrative files, correspondence, and personnel files, A-H, UA001-100 (Box 36)
    The material contains administrative files relating to the Tufts' security agreements with the U.S. Department of Defense, correspondence between Tufts and the U.S. Department of Defense, correspondence and agreements with the Atomic Energy Commission, and confidential files on all personnel with security clearance.
  - Department of Defense personnel files, H-Z, UA001-101 (Box 37)
  - Mayer - Andre Mayer (father) materials, UA001-102 (Box 38)
  - Mayer - Clippings, publications, slides/media, datebooks, UA001-103 (Box 39)
  - Bacow - Talloires Conference Site Backup, 2005; UA001-104
    This digital object contains photographs and other digital files from the website for President Bacow's conference, entitled "The Civic Engagement Roles and Responsibilities of Higher Education." This conference was hosted by Tufts University in September 15-17, 2005 at the Tufts University European Center in Talloires, France.
  - Plans and reports for new music building and master planning records, 2004; UA001-105 (Box 40)
    Plans and reports for new music building, 2004, and one folder of historical master planning records relevant to the project